{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "She looks ___ than she is.",
      "a": "more younger",
      "b": "very younger",
      "c": "more young",
      "d": "much younger",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Much + comparative form of adj + than",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jane liked her new hat so much that she wouldn't ___.",
      "a": "take it off",
      "b": "take off it",
      "c": "put it off",
      "d": "put off it",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- take sth off = to remove something from a place",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Breakfast is ready. Let's go ___.",
      "a": "downstairs",
      "b": "the downstairs",
      "c": "to downstair",
      "d": "to downstairs",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Go downstairs/upstairs",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where is he going? \"He is going ___\"",
      "a": "to home",
      "b": "home",
      "c": "at home",
      "d": "for home",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- go home (no prepositions)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you know your results? No, I don't know them ___.",
      "a": "already",
      "b": "since",
      "c": "before",
      "d": "yet",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Negative form + yet",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "He does not like a child,___ a baby.",
      "a": "much less",
      "b": "still more",
      "c": "much worse",
      "d": "more",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- much less: used to say that a greater thing is even less true, likely, or possible than the thing you have just mentioned.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "The actuality is ___ stern a thing for sentiment.",
      "a": "as",
      "b": "much",
      "c": "too",
      "d": "so",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Too .... for + n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "My brother _________ alone at night.",
      "a": "seldom go out",
      "b": "seldom goes out",
      "c": "goes seldom out",
      "d": "goes out seldom",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Seldom goes out\n- Seldom (abv): very rarely or almost never.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "He was too tired to go ___ farther.",
      "a": "still",
      "b": "some",
      "c": "any",
      "d": "no",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Any: used before the comparative form of an adjective to mean \"even a small amount\".",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Don't be long. \" ___\"",
      "a": "Yes, please do so",
      "b": "Yes, I am",
      "c": "No, I am not",
      "d": "No, I won't",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Don't ..... No, I won't",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "5"
    }
  ]
}